Guide to the Rose Goldsen papers, [ca. 1950-1985]
Goldsen, Rose papers, [ca. 1950-1985]
- Series VI Subject Files
  - Funding Sources
    - National Science Foundation - Toronto, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - National Telecommunications and Information Administration (NTIA) (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - New York Council for the Humanities (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Foundations R-W (miscellaneous) (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Rockefeller Humanities Fellowship 9/80 (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Twentieth Century Fund (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Wilson Center (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Extracurricular Activities (filed alphabetically)
    - Bob Beggs - Chapter for book on World Community (Box 17, Folder 30)
      [corresp. 4-12/78]
    - Extra-Curricular - unclassified (Box 17, Folder 31)
      [Women's Study Group, 9/82; Ithaca Community Radio 10/82]
    - Journal of Social Reconstruction (Box 17, Folder 32)
      [corresp w/ Marcus Raskin, Susan Buck-Morss, 8/78-5/80]
    - NCCB [Ntl. Citizens Committee for Broadcasting] Academ; Advisory Committee (and Speaker's Bureau) (Box 17, Folder 33)
      [corresp w/ Samuel A. Simon, Sally Steenland, George Gerbner 1/79-8/81]
    - National Citizens Communications Lobby (NCCL) (Box 17, Folder 34)
      [corresp w/ Melinda Halpert, Townes Osborn 4/78-5/79]
    - Poetry Seminar 4/14/84 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Projecto Caribeno de Justicia y Paz (Nelson Colon, Sam Silva) (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Alphabetical Subject Files
    - Access Issues
      - Access to TV by federal, city and state governments (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - "Neighborhood TV" (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Ad Hoc Networks (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Alaska Television (Box 23, Folder 4)
        RKG notes
    - Alternatives To Present Broadcast System
      - NCCB: Audience Network (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Phil Olenick: Communications Credits (Box 23, Folder 6)
        National Citizens Committee for Broadcasting
    - Animation
      - Animating Children's Literature, Animals (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - Animation - Unclassified (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Archives
      - Intermedia Archives and Vanderbilt Tapes (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - TV Archives, Film Archives (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - TV Libraries (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - AUTOS, Auto Industry
      - Automobile and Habitat Evolve Each Other (Box 23, Folder 12)
        RKG notes c 30pp
      - Automobile - History and Future (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - Autos - Unclassified (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Awards
      - Awards - Unclassified (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - Humanitas Prize (Box 23, Folder 16)
      - Taba Book Awards (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Bibliography
      - Advertising (Box 23, Folder 18)
      - Bibliography - Unclassified (Box 23, Folder 19)
      - Children/Socialization/ Development (Box 23, Folder 20)
        Kate Moody letter to RKG
      - Communication (Box 23, Folder 21)
      - Documentaries (Box 23, Folder 22)
      - Film, Video (Box 23, Folder 23)
      - Information (Box 23, Folder 24)
      - Journals (Box 23, Folder 25)
      - Mass Media/Mass Communication (Box 23, Folder 26)
      - News and Journalism (Box 23, Folder 27)
      - Special Interest Works - Marxist, Structuralist, Semiotics (Box 23, Folder 28)
      - Television (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Boycotts (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Brain Lateralization: Neurophysiology, Heuristics
      - Brain Activity and Development (Box 23, Folder 31)
      - Brain Lateralization -Unclassified (Box 23, Folder 32)
      - Event Related Potential and Decision Making (Box 23, Folder 33)
        Sociology 252; 20pp
      - Lecture 15 - Split Brain (3/28/78) (Box 23, Folder 34)
      - Lecture 16 - Eye (Box 23, Folder 35)
      - Left/Right Brain -"Lateralization" (Box 23, Folder 36)
        8pp
      - Memory and Brain Structure (Box 23, Folder 37)
      - TV and Brain Activity (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Cable
      - Access (Box 23, Folder 39)
      - American Television and Communications Corp. (Box 23, Folder 40)
      - Cable Legislation - S66 (1983), HR (Box 23, Folder 41)
        RLG statement 6/13/77, 7pp; notes 10 pp
      - Cable TV - Canada, Britain (Box 23, Folder 42)
      - Cable Commercials (Box 23, Folder 43)
      - Cable Companies - unclassified (Box 23, Folder 44)
      - FCC Regulatory History (Box 23, Folder 45)
      - Franchise Bids/Issues (Box 23, Folder 46)
      - Interactive Cable (Box 23, Folder 47)
        RKG notes 1p
      - Ithaca and Tompkins County (Box 23, Folder 48)
        RKG article draft, notes 8pp.
      - Cable TV lecture (Box 23, Folder 49)
      - Local Monopoly (Box 23, Folder 50)
        RKG notes 4 pp
      - D. Nash & J. Smith - Privacy (Box 23, Folder 51)
      - Network Project Notebooks (Box 23, Folder 52)
      - Pay Cable 1979-80 (Box 23, Folder 53)
      - Cable TV Shows Available (Box 23, Folder 54)
      - Cable TV - Summary (1971) (Box 23, Folder 55)
      - Superstations, Copyright (Box 23, Folder 56)
      - Cable TV - Unclassified (Box 23, Folder 57)
    - Cable Networks
      - Cable - Networks, Services (Box 23, Folder 58)
      - Cable Networks - unclassified RKG notes 4pp (Box 23, Folder 59)
      - CBS Cable (Box 23, Folder 60)
      - ESPN Network (owned by Getty Oil) (Box 23, Folder 61)
      - Madison Square Garden/USA Network (Box 23, Folder 62)
      - Pace Network - public cable network (Carnegie Corporation proposal) (Box 23, Folder 63)
      - Premier Network (Getty Oil Company) (Box 23, Folder 64)
    - Campaign Analysis, Review, Comment - Mostly 1980
      - Anderson - 1980 (Box 23, Folder 65)
      - Archie Bunker, Walter Cronkite -1980 Campaign (Box 23, Folder 66)
      - Campaign Post-Mortem After 1980 Election (Box 23, Folder 67)
      - Carter Staff - 1980 (Box 23, Folder 68)
      - Debates - Pre-convention (Box 23, Folder 69)
      - Debates - 1980 Campaign (Box 23, Folder 70)
      - Democratic Convention 1980 (Box 23, Folder 71)
      - Fairness Issues - 1979-80 Campaign (Box 23, Folder 72)
      - Ted Kennedy - 1980 (Box 23, Folder 73)
      - Media Consultants (Box 23, Folder 74)
      - Network Coverage - 1980 Campaign (Box 23, Folder 75)
      - 1980 Campaign - Unclassified (Box 23, Folder 76)
      - "Other" Candidates (Box 23, Folder 77)
      - Polls - "Horse Race" Reporting (Box 23, Folder 78)
      - Primaries and Caucuses - Iowa, Ohio (i960) (Box 23, Folder 79)
      - Primaries 1983 (Box 23, Folder 80)
      - Reagan 1980 (Box 23, Folder 81)
      - Republican Convention - 1980/ Bush-Ford Story (Box 23, Folder 82)
      - Staff (All Candidates) - 1980 Campaign (Box 23, Folder 83)
    - Commercials
      - Commercials - Presidential Campaign 1980 (Box 23, Folder 84)
      - How Commercials Work (Box 23, Folder 85)
      - Senate and House Campaign Commercials (Box 23, Folder 86)
      - Stoner Campaign Ads - Racial Slurs (Box 23, Folder 87)
      - Why Political TV Spots Should Be Banned (Box 23, Folder 88)
    - Campaign Spending
      - Campaign Spending 1970-73 (Box 23, Folder 89)
      - Campaign Spending 1973-74 RKG notes 2 pp (Box 23, Folder 90)
      - Campaign Spending 1975 (Box 23, Folder 91)
      - Campaign Spending 1978-80 (Box 23, Folder 92)
      - Financial Disclosure (Box 23, Folder 93)
      - Visa/banks (Box 23, Folder 94)
    - Censorship (Box 23, Folder 95)
    - Checkbook Journalism
      - Checkbook Journalism -Unclassified (Box 23, Folder 96)
      - Haldeman (Box 23, Folder 97)
      - E.B. White-Xerox Correspondence (Soc. 100.2) (Box 23, Folder 98)
        RKG letter to EB White 6/22/76
    - Children's Cognitive Processes
      - Children's Cognitive Processes -Unclassified (Box 23, Folder 99)
      - Language Environments (Box 23, Folder 100)
        Memo to RKG, with paper, by Donald P. Hayes, Cornell Sociology, n.d.
      - Quarforth, J: Children's Understanding of TV Characters (Box 23, Folder 101)
      - Singer, Singer, et al: TV Viewing and Preschoolers' Behavior (Box 23, Folder 102)
    - Children's Programming
      - Advertising Practices - ProposedRules (Box 23, Folder 103)
      - Children's Programming -Unclassified (Box 23, Folder 104)
      - Communications Act of 1979 (Box 23, Folder 105)
      - Economics of Children's TV (Box 23, Folder 106)
        RKG letter to Dr. Alan Pierce, FCC 9/20/74; article by Pierce
      - Evaluations and Improvement Suggestions (Box 23, Folder 107)
      - Reports and Conferences (Box 23, Folder 108)
        Invitational letter to RKG from Michael Rice, Aspen Institute, re: mtg on Children & TV
      - Vice Versa Vision (Box 23, Folder 109)
        Clippings, RKG notes c 3pp
    - Children's Television Workshop (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Cigarettes and Tobacco (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Cleveland (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Commercials, Advertising And Promotion
      - Ad Agencies (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Ads, Commercials - Unclassified (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Advertiser Pressure, Control of Program Content (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Advertising Theory (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Ambiguous "Who?" (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - M. Arlen - New Yorker Articles (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Aylesworth - Herbert Hoover on Radio Ads (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - Bar Commercials - Beer as Reward (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - CBS Bicentennial Minutes (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - China (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - Chinese Motif - Bloomingdale's Ads (Box 24, Folder 14)
        Ann Bouslog notes RKG 9/29/80
      - Chiquita Banana - United Fruit Co. (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - Cigarette Ads - US/South America/Africa/W. Germany (Box 24, Folder 16)
      - Coke and Pepsi (Box 24, Folder 17)
      - Commercials Creating Structure (Box 24, Folder 18)
      - Content and Meaning (Box 24, Folder 19)
        RKG notes 5pp
      - Demise of Mother Role In Ads (Box 24, Folder 20)
      - Dr. Pepper, "Be A Pepper" and Imitations (Box 24, Folder 21)
      - Ewen, Stuart - "Advertising as Social Production" (Box 24, Folder 22)
      - Feedback Techniques in Ads (Box 24, Folder 23)
      - Foods, Nutrition (Box 24, Folder 24)
      - Formula Ads - Super heroes, Romance (Box 24, Folder 25)
      - Future Prospects (Box 24, Folder 26)
      - Hazards - Nasal Sprays, Nestle Infant Formula (Box 24, Folder 27)
      - Hidden Commercials - Associated Film Productions (Box 24, Folder 28)
        RKG correspondence and notes of phone conversation, w/AFP
      - Conversation, w/ Hidden Commercials - Visual Blurbs and Plugs (Box 24, Folder 29)
      - High Tech Ads (Box 24, Folder 30)
      - History of Advertising (Box 24, Folder 31)
      - How Ads Work; What They Try to Do (Box 24, Folder 32)
      - How Commercials Are Bought and Sold (Box 24, Folder 33)
      - How Commercials Work -Acknowledgements by Industry Spokesmen (Box 24, Folder 34)
      - Japanese Commercials (Box 24, Folder 35)
      - Leading National Advertisers 1977-8 (Box 24, Folder 36)
      - A. Kent McDougal Columns (Los Angeles Times) (Box 24, Folder 37)
      - Mobil Ad - Lamenting the Fallen Sparrow (Box 24, Folder 38)
        RKG notes 7pp
      - Movies/Tales/Myths/Scripts (Box 24, Folder 39)
      - Newsbreaks/ Instant News (Box 24, Folder 40)
      - New York Times ad (extensional thrust) (Box 24, Folder 41)
      - Political Ads (Box 24, Folder 42)
        Stephen Silverman - Soc 252 paper, 5/83
      - Positioning (Box 24, Folder 43)
        RKG radio script, "Repositioning Massagers," 11/16-17/79
      - Pregnancy Test Kits, Contraceptives, Artificial Insemination (Box 24, Folder 44)
      - Premiums/Coupons (Box 24, Folder 45)
      - Production Spectaculars (Box 24, Folder 46)
      - Professions - Accountants, Lawyers, etc. (Box 24, Folder 47)
      - Public Service Announcements (PSAs) (Box 24, Folder 48)
      - Soaps, Cosmetics, and Perfumes (Box 24, Folder 49)
      - Ten Second Spot Commercials (Box 24, Folder 50)
      - Toilet Paper (Box 24, Folder 51)
      - Toy Promotions (Box 24, Folder 52)
      - Tylenol (Box 24, Folder 53)
        Colleen McGee, "The Tylenol Comeback," Soc 252, 5/83
      - "You and the Commercial" (CBS Documentary) - Student Papers- Several Soc 152 papers, with RKG comments, 11/76 (Box 24, Folder 54)
    - Advertising Vehicles
      - Advertising Vehicles-Unclassified (Box 24, Folder 55)
      - Movie Theater Commercials (Box 24, Folder 56)
      - On-Line Media (Box 24, Folder 57)
    - Children
      - Children - Unclassified (Box 24, Folder 58)
      - Children and Youth Market (Box 24, Folder 59)
        Lauren Turner Soc 252 paper, nd
      - Children's Game Promotions (Box 24, Folder 60)
      - Jeans Ads, Toys (Box 24, Folder 61)
        RKG radio script (draft) 11/22-23/80, RKG notes 7pp
    - Corporate Advertising
      - Advocacy Advertising (Box 24, Folder 62)
      - Banks (Box 24, Folder 63)
        RKG notes, "Banks and Giveaways," 1pp
      - Corporate Advertising/ Phase II (Box 24, Folder 64)
      - Corporate Ads - Unclassified (Box 24, Folder 65)
      - Corporate Identity Positioning (Box 24, Folder 66)
      - Institutional Advertising (Box 24, Folder 67)
    - Explicit Ads
      - Phallic and Vaginal Symbols (Box 24, Folder 68)
      - References to Sex/Intercourse/ Foreplay/Nudity (Box 24, Folder 69)
      - Sexy Ads - Discussion and Commentary (Box 24, Folder 70)
        RKG notes 2pp
      - Sexy Ads - Examples (Box 24, Folder 71)
      - S.M. (Sadomasochism) (Box 24, Folder 72)
      - Toilet (Box 24, Folder 73)
    - Presenters In Commercials
      - American Association of Advertising Agencies - study of viewer understanding, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 74)
      - Athletes, Sports (Box 24, Folder 75)
      - Bruzzone Research Company (BRC) - direct response tests of commercials, 1978-79 correspondence commercials, 1978-79 (Box 24, Folder 76)
        RKG Bruzzone correspondence
      - Casting (Box 24, Folder 77)
      - Continuing Characters in Commercials, Product Spokesmen (Box 24, Folder 78)
      - Heads of State, US Presidents (Box 24, Folder 79)
      - Human Celebrities in Commercials (Box 24, Folder 80)
      - Presenters - Rationale, Production Techniques (Box 24, Folder 81)
      - Presenters - unclassified (Box 24, Folder 82)
      - Voices/Voice-Overs, Look-alikes (Box 24, Folder 83)
    - Communications Act
      - Annenberg School Survey - Summer 1979 (Box 24, Folder 84)
      - Communications Act - 1977 (Box 24, Folder 85)
      - Communications Act 1978 - HR 13015 (Box 24, Folder 86)
        RKG notes 4pp
      - Communications Act 1979 - HR 3333, S 622 (Box 24, Folder 87)
        Invitational letter to RKG from Lionel Van Deerlin, chair of House Subcommittee on Communications, to speak at hearing 6/79
      - Communications Act 1980 (Box 24, Folder 88)
      - Communications Act 1981-2 (Box 24, Folder 89)
      - Testimony Before House Subcommittee on Communications -6/79 (Box 24, Folder 90)
      - Texts of 5 testimonies; RKG's not included here (Box 24, Folder 91)
    - Communications Policy And Technology
      - Audio Technology (Box 24, Folder 92)
      - Bibliography (Box 24, Folder 93)
      - Les Brown: Blurb for Channels (Box 24, Folder 94)
      - Carter Administration (Box 24, Folder 95)
      - Communications Policy and Technology - Unclassified (Box 24, Folder 96)
      - Communications Revolution -Notes (Box 24, Folder 97)
        RKG notes 19pp
      - Communications Technologies - Clippings Early 1970s (Box 24, Folder 98)
      - Communications Technology - RKG Notes (Box 24, Folder 99)
        7pp
      - Communications Technology and Social Organization (Box 24, Folder 100)
      - Data Banks: Access (Box 24, Folder 101)
      - Dubbing (Box 24, Folder 102)
        RKG notes 3pp
      - Electronic Banking (Box 24, Folder 103)
      - Electronic Mail, Facsimile Machines (Box 24, Folder 104)
      - FCC - Network Inquiry 1980 (Box 24, Folder 105)
      - Fiber Optics (Box 24, Folder 106)
      - French Sources (Box 24, Folder 107)
      - Holography (Box 24, Folder 108)
      - International Institute of Communication: Issues in Communications 1 (1977) (Box 24, Folder 109)
      - International Telecommunications Union: Issues and Next Steps (1971) (Box 24, Folder 110)
      - NCCB-Final Report on New Communications Technologies (1979) (Box 24, Folder 111)
      - News and Technology (Box 24, Folder 112)
      - Overviews - 1977+ (Box 24, Folder 113)
      - Packet Switching/Weapons Systems (Box 24, Folder 114)
      - Privacy Issues (Box 24, Folder 115)
      - Remote Sensing (Box 24, Folder 116)
      - Telecommunications and Society 1976-1991 (Arthur D. little, Inc.) (Box 24, Folder 117)
      - Telephone (Box 24, Folder 118)
      - Television Technologies (Box 24, Folder 119)
      - Television Technologies and the Networks (Box 24, Folder 120)
      - video (Box 24, Folder 121)
    - Videotex, Teletext, Telematics
      - CBS - Teletext (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - France - Telematics, Videotex (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Prestel (Britain) (Box 25, Folder 3)
        RKG radio script 8/4-7/79
      - Telematics - Overview (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Videotex, Teletext - Overview (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Videotex, Teletext - Unclassified (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Computers
      - Artificial Intelligence (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Bibliography (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Companies in Computer Technology (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - Computer Breakdowns, Failsafe (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - Computer Games (Box 25, Folder 11)
      - Computer Graphics, Music, Voice Recognition (Box 25, Folder 12)
      - Computer Networks (Box 25, Folder 13)
      - Computer Tampering (Hackers) (Box 25, Folder 14)
        RKG radio script (draft) 10/16-7/83
      - Computers and Social Policy (Box 25, Folder 15)
      - Computers - Overviews (Box 25, Folder 16)
      - Computers - Unclassified (Box 25, Folder 17)
      - Crime and Criminals (Box 25, Folder 18)
      - Democratic Process and Computers (Box 25, Folder 19)
      - Microprocessors, Microchips, Semiconductors paper, 5/80, w/ (Box 25, Folder 20)
        Lewis Clark Soc 462 paper, 5/80, w/RKG comments; notes 7 pp
      - Public Interest Computer Association (Box 25, Folder 21)
      - Schools, School Systems (Box 25, Folder 22)
      - Surveillance (Box 25, Folder 23)
      - Workplace, Jobs (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Home Computers And Communications
      - ATT Directory Service (Box 25, Folder 25)
      - Consumer Electronics -Advertising Acre special issue (Box 25, Folder 26)
      - Home Computer Options (Box 25, Folder 27)
      - Home Information Systems: "Information Utility" (Box 25, Folder 28)
      - Home Video Market (Box 25, Folder 29)
      - Industry Trends (Box 25, Folder 30)
      - Personal Computer Networks (Box 25, Folder 31)
      - M. Rogers, "Children of UNIVAC: Small Computers... " (Box 25, Folder 32)
      - The Source, Compu-Serve (Box 25, Folder 33)
      - "Teleshopping" (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Congressional Oversight
      - House Subcommittee on Communications (Box 25, Folder 35)
      - House Subcommittee on Telecommunications, Consumer Affairs and Finance - 1981 (Box 25, Folder 36)
      - Senate Subcommittee on Communications (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Congressional Telecasts (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - Consumer Issues
      - Car Rentals (Box 25, Folder 39)
      - Consumer Product Safety Commission (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Content Analysis
      - Business and Media (Box 25, Folder 41)
      - Casting for TV - Social Typing (Box 25, Folder 42)
        RKG, "Stereotype and Mass Communications" (typbescript) Pat Aufderheide (In These Times) letter to RKG, nd
      - Children in TV, Films (Box 25, Folder 43)
      - Cities (Box 25, Folder 44)
      - Content Analysis - Unclassified (Box 25, Folder 45)
      - The Day After (Box 25, Folder 46)
        RKG radio script 11/22/83, 12/4-5/83 ("The Crisis Game")
      - Death/Execution/Grief/Mourning (Box 25, Folder 47)
      - Drug Use - TV, Comic Books (Box 25, Folder 48)
        Note to RKG from Hector [Velez?], nd
      - Government and Law (Box 25, Folder 49)
      - Guns and Violence (Box 25, Folder 50)
      - Health and Illness (Box 25, Folder 51)
      - Hitler Era (Box 25, Folder 52)
      - Imported Television (Box 25, Folder 53)
      - Mental Health and Psychotherapy (Box 25, Folder 54)
        RKG radio script "Psycho-Viewing," 4/29-5/2/78
      - Miscellaneous TV Shows (Box 25, Folder 55)
      - National Drivers Test (CBS) 104 (Box 25, Folder 56)
        RKG notes 9pp
      - Presidential Language (Box 25, Folder 57)
      - Schools - TV Images (Box 25, Folder 58)
      - Science and Scientists (Box 25, Folder 59)
      - Sensationalism in 18th Century Newspapers (Box 25, Folder 60)
      - Sit-coms (Box 25, Folder 61)
      - Village Voice (Box 25, Folder 62)
      - Workers and TV (Box 25, Folder 63)
    - Stratification
      - Aged (Box 25, Folder 64)
      - Amos 'n1 Andy, Minstrel Shows (Box 25, Folder 65)
      - Genderspeak (Box 25, Folder 66)
      - Handicapped (Box 25, Folder 67)
      - Media "Liberation"/Women = Market (Box 25, Folder 68)
      - Minorities and Women on TV (Box 25, Folder 69)
      - Occupations, Class, Race and Ethnicity on TV (Box 25, Folder 70)
        RKG notes 13pp
      - "Of Women and Men" (NEC); NEC Sex Discrimination (Box 25, Folder 71)
        RKG radio script, "Of Women and Men," 1/18-20/75; RKG notes 18 pp
      - Race, Ethnicity and the Media (Box 25, Folder 72)
      - Race, Ethnicity and TV (Box 25, Folder 73)
        RKG notes 5pp; Ralph Stavins (IPS) letter to RKG 10/12/72
      - Race, Ethnicity and TV - Student Papers (Box 25, Folder 74)
        With RKG comments
      - Sexploitation - TV (Box 25, Folder 75)
      - Women and Sex Roles -Unclassified (Box 25, Folder 76)
      - Women as Witches (Box 25, Folder 77)
      - Women in the News in Colombia (Box 25, Folder 78)
        Cornelia Flora corresp 2-3/74
      - Women, Sex Roles and Commercials (Box 25, Folder 79)
      - Women, Sex Roles and the Media (Box 25, Folder 80)
      - Women, Sex Roles and Television (Box 25, Folder 81)
        RKG notes 8pp; Harold Kohn letter to RKG, 1974
      - Working Women on TV (Box 25, Folder 82)
    - Copyright Issues And Piracy
      - Copyright Issues (Box 25, Folder 83)
      - Piracy - Films, Music, TV (Box 25, Folder 84)
    - Corporate Environment
      - Corporate Environment -Unclassified (Box 25, Folder 85)
      - Corporate TV (Box 25, Folder 86)
      - Foreign Investment (Box 25, Folder 87)
      - ITT - Advertising, TV Sponsor ships (Box 25, Folder 88)
        RKG radio script, "Big Blue Marble..," 10/5-7/74; notes 5pp
      - ITT - Anti-Trust Case, Watergate (Box 25, Folder 89)
      - ITT, Chile, CIA (Box 25, Folder 90)
      - ITT -Continental Banking, Levitt (Box 25, Folder 91)
      - Oregon Public Utility Commission (Box 25, Folder 92)
      - Vesco, Figueres (Box 25, Folder 93)
    - Courts, Court Cases
      - Courtroom Telecasts (Box 25, Folder 94)
      - Ford-Pinto Trial, 1980 (Indiana) (Box 25, Folder 95)
      - Robert W. Nelson murder case (Box 25, Folder 96)
      - Ronney Zamora case, Miami 1977 - Ellis Rubin, defense attorney (Box 25, Folder 97)
        RKG, "Watching Zamora Trial," Ithaca New Times 10/18/77; notes; Rubin correspondence
      - Video Testimony (Box 25, Folder 98)
    - Cultural Heroes, Celebrities
      - All in the Family/Smithsonian Institution (Box 25, Folder 99)
      - Lucille Ball (Box 25, Folder 100)
      - Cultural Heroes/Celebrities - unclassified (Box 25, Folder 101)
      - Elvis Presley (Box 25, Folder 102)
      - John Wayne (Box 25, Folder 103)
    - Decentralized Networks
      - Hayes, Peter: Notes on Transitional Networks (Box 25, Folder 104)
      - Y. Masuda: Future Perspectives on the Information Utility (Box 25, Folder 105)
    - Definitional Control
      - Definitional Control -Unclassified (Box 25, Folder 106)
      - Dow Jones vs. Meat Prices (Box 25, Folder 107)